Pull yourself together.
振作点
Do you want to die on your first day?
入伍当天就想死吗
Do it now.
就是现在
Get crushed!
压碎你
You must live on.
你要活下去
What is going on here?
这到底是怎么回事
Do not let go of the RED Strings.
别放开…别解开红色系线
Good morning.
早安
The weather is great today.
今天一整天都是好天气
We have no mission this morning.
中午前没有任务
Would you go out with me? There's a place I want to visit.
要不要出去走走 我有想去的地方
Baki!
吐吐神
SCARLET NEXUS
《绯红结系》
♪A crime in reality♪
现实的Crimｅ
♪For Heaven's sake♪
For Heaven's sake
♪Accepts any fake♪
接受虚假
♪And disappears piling the eternity in fantasy♪
永恒的幻想 层层逝去
♪Won't take it at all, I get sick♪
绝非完美 I get sick
♪A girl looking back♪
转身而来的少女
♪Casts the miracle into this instant world♪
在这瞬息世界中 落下了奇迹
♪Did you lie♪
Did you lie
♪Spit the venom♪
Spit the venom
♪I know why♪
I know why
♪I've found a game of ecstasy♪
找到了 绝顶的游戏
♪Red Criminal gets life♪
Red Criminal gets life
♪I've never been in love♪
I've never been in love
♪Don't know when I started getting sick of this world♪
我何时开始厌倦了这样的世界
♪We will fly♪
We will fly
♪Someday I won't be crying♪
Someday I won't be crying
♪I've been sacrificing myself not to hurt anybody♪
为了不再伤害 而牺牲了自己
SCARLET GUARDIANS
(绯红守护者)
Up next, we have Other attack forecast for each province.
以下是来自怪异省的怪异预报
The probability for Suoh Capital is 10%.
苏芳京附近出现机率10%
For Seiran, it's 15%.
青蓝市附近出现机率15%
The probability for Togetsu is 12%.
渡月地方附近出现机率12%
"OTHERS TODAY" The Extinction Belt is at the stratosphere.
(今日的怪异) 断绝之带在平流层附近
There is currently no impact on the surface.
目前对地面上并无影响
There is a higher chance of it approaching certain areas in the afternoon.
下午靠近某些地域的可能性较高
-I think the person who saved me was Kasane. -Please stay cautious at all times.
-我觉得 那个人应该是重 -还请多加小心
How is that possible?
怎么可能
But members of OSF might have stunted growth.
可是 怪伐军的队员 也可能被抑制了成长
You have a point. Appearances can be deceptive in OSF.
这倒是 光看怪伐军的外表是不准的
2nd Lieutenant Arashi Spring is the elder sister.
岚诗宾大尉是姊姊
Major General Fubuki is the younger brother instead.
吹雪诗宾连队长反而是弟弟
The age and the appearances have no direct relations.
因为年纪与外表无关
So there is basically no need for honorific titles.
所以基本上不需要尊称
Ignore the ranks and titles, what matters is true strength.
无须在乎阶级 实力至上
Captain Seto said so himself.
赛特队长是这么说的
But Kasane and Naomi are both amateurs just like us.
可是 重和直见 跟我们一样是菜鸟喔
They are only 16 years old.
年纪都是16岁
Even though Naomi is the elder sister,
就算直见是大姊姊
I'm not going to change my mind.
我的心意还是不变
I'm sorry to take up your time.
抱歉 让妳陪我出来
If I let you go out alone, you might attract creeps.
只让姊姊一人出门 可能会招引到怪东西
All of us have powers.
我们每个人都拥有"脑力"
Thanks to our powers,
多亏了这个能力
we cannot only access psynet
不仅能链接超脑网络
but also use it for many things
还能做许多事
such as shopping.
可以买东西
PAYMENT COMPLETED
(支付完毕)
We can search for information and send messages.
搜寻信息 还能传递讯息
Some of us have power,
当中拥有超强脑力 "超脑力"的人
they are the OSF.
他们就是 怪伐军
Scarlet Guardians!
绯红守护者
Yakumo Sumeragi.
八云皇
He saved mankind from total annihilation with the Spring of Extinction.
以"断绝之春" 拯救了差点被灭绝的人类
He is the founding father of New Himuka.
新日向的建国之父
A great man indeed.
果然了不起
Your ancestor's grave is now a tourism destination.
你祖先的墓地 现在是观光景点了
He was born over 2000 years ago.
他是两千年前的人
So I don't feel any relation in particular.
我也没什么感觉
There it is.
有了
BAKI TALISMAN
(吐吐神御神签)
An omikuji event in collaboration with Baki.
与吐吐神合作的抽签活动
Even the founding father is fashionable.
建国之父也挺跟上时代的嘛
Yuito, Nagi.
结人 那歧
Naomi and Kasane!
直见 重
Are you here for the omikuji too?
你们也来抽御神签吗
I'm here with Yuito.
我陪结人来的
I ask Kasane to come with me.
我请重陪我来的
Yuito, do you like Baki too?
结人也喜欢吐吐神吗
-Well... -Now that we are here,
-算喜… -来都来了
let's have some tea after this.
抽完御神签后 去喝杯茶吧
There is still some time before our mission this afternoon.
离下午出任务还有段时间
Sister, beware of this man.
姊姊 小心
I knew I should have come with you.
还好我有跟来
-Did I do something wrong? -Kasane...
-我做了什么吗 -重
What is it?
干嘛
Kasane, Naomi, do you have a sister that is much older than you?
重 直见 妳们还有大许多岁数的姊姊吗
Kasane is my only sibling.
我家只有我和重姊妹二人喔
Do you have any relatives who joined OSF in the past?
那是否是亲戚曾加入怪伐军
No. Why do you ask?
没有 怎么了
Let's draw the omikuji now.
先去抽签吧
Then we'll have some tea together!
快点抽完一起去喝茶
"GREAT DISASTER"
(大凶)
Sister, what did you get?
姊姊抽到什么
Great prosperity.
大吉
Everyone got the worst omikuji ever except for Naomi.
除了直见 其他人都抽到大凶
At least not all of us will get bad luck.
至少不是全部都大凶
But we have an OSF mission afterward.
可是 我们之后 要执行怪伐军的任务
This is a bad omen.
太不吉利了
It's such a buzzkill.
害我都没兴致了
Don't throw it away, Nagi.
那歧 不可以乱丢
Yuito!
结人 你…
-Give it to me. -Sorry!
-给我 -抱歉抱歉
Yuito and Nagi, give me yours.
结人的 那歧的也给我
Tie it like this.
这样绑
This should turn your bad luck into lesser good luck.
好了 大家的运势就变成小吉了
Let's give it our best from now on.
之后 大家一起加油吧
You are so gentle and kind, Naomi!
温柔 直见真的好温柔喔
Your kindness saved us all!
妳的温柔拯救了大家
You saved me too! This is great!
我也被妳拯救了 太棒了
The Seiran front?
青蓝方面军
Where is it this time?
这次是在哪
It's an abandoned underground railway line, it's near the Suoh Nine.
在废弃地下轨道苏芳九号线附近
Just as we mentioned before,
跟之前的说法一样
they are going in to investigate the Other activity.
说是为了调查怪异
They refuse to heed our advice despite the objection.
无论抗议了几次 他们仍是不听吗
Send in backups.
追加戒备人员
Yes. There's another report
是 另外…
we have yet to verify.
还有个尚未证实的情报
There are some suspicious activities in Togetsu.
渡月的行动似乎有些可疑
The Moon is stirring up troubles again.
这些相信月球的麻烦家伙们
I will report after the investigation has been completed.
等情报更明确后 我再跟您报告
I'll leave it to you.
交给你了
Minister.
本部长…
No, Kaito.
不 界人
Yes.
是
How is Yuito doing?
结人的情况怎么样
I saw the report of him defeating an Other.
我看到他打倒怪异的报导
I didn't get a chance to talk to him after he joined the army.
他入伍之后 我还没机会跟他对话
I know he is my brother, but I can't give him any special treatments.
即便我们是兄弟 也不能对他有特别待遇
I see. You have a point.
这样啊 也是
That's all for the report today.
今天的报告到此为止
I should leave now.
我先告辞了
The Seirans are on the move again.
青蓝似乎开始行动了
Let them be.
随便他们
What did I...
我…到底…
What's wrong, Yuito?
结人 怎么了
It's nothing.
没事…
Everyone is here.
大家都到齐啦
The joint beginner training of Seto Platoon and Kyoka Platoon
赛特小队和镜花小队的 欢迎菜鸟共同特训
is about to begin.
就要开始啰
A joint training?
共同特训
The rule is simple.
规则很简单
It's a 5v5 simulation battle between Seto Platoon and Kyoka Platoon.
赛特小队五人对上 镜花小队五人的模拟战
The first team to secure the flag in the middle wins.
先抢到位于正中央旗帜的小队获胜
There are only four in Kyoka Platoon.
镜花小队只有四人
Arashi!
岚
Arashi, shutting down.
岚 程序关闭中
Don't fall asleep!
不准睡觉
She seems different from the TV.
怎么跟平常在屏幕上的感觉不同
When we saw her online and on the news...
在网络和电视上看到的岚…
I will give it my best too!
岚 非常努力唷
That's when she's at work.
那是营业模式啦
What we see here is her usual self.
岚平常都是那副模样
People in the OSF call her Lazy Arashi.
怪伐军内都称她"蛋黄岚"
Fine, let's get it over with.
好吧 尽快解决
Okay, everyone.
好 各就各位
Let's do our best.
互相加油吧
Okay.
好
It's done, Kasane.
重 好了
This is the proof of our bond as sisters.
这是我和重是姊妹的证明
-Sister. What is it?
-姊姊 -什么事
Are you concerned about Yuito?
你是不是很在意结人
Kasane, what made you say that?
重 妳怎么突然这么问
I'm not particularly concerned...
也不算在意…
I just find him a nice person.
就是…觉得还不错…
Understood.
我知道了
Whether he is qualified to be with you,
我去帮姊姊确认
I will find it out.
他是否配得上姐姐
Kasane!
重
"MAJOR SHIDEN RITTER, POWER: ELECTROKINESIS" Young Master of the Sumeragi family.
(紫电里特中尉 超脑力：放电) 皇家的小少爷
"CAPTAIN GEMMA GARRISON" He defeated an Other
(盖曼加里森大尉) 他初次上场实战就打倒了怪异
"POWER: SCLEROKINESIS" on his first day.
(超脑力：硬质化)
Don't let your guard down around him, Shiden.
紫电 别大意
All right.
好
"HARUKA FRAZER, POWER: TELEPATHY" It's about to start.
(遥弗雷泽少尉 超脑力：精神感应) 准备开始啰
Ready,
Ready
go!
Go
Kasane!
重
Watch out for the flame!
小心别被烧伤啰
It started.
开始了
"MAJOR KYOKA EDEN, POWER: DUPLICATION" Go for it, everyone!
(镜花伊登少佐 超脑力：复制) 各位 加油喔
Naomi, sorry about that.
直见 抱歉啰
It's the same trick as before.
这是之前的那招
My power is clairvoyance.
我的超脑力 预知未来
I can foresee the future in an instant.
我能在一瞬间看到未来景象
I'm too lazy to move.
我懒…
I see it.
看到了
Not bad, Gemma.
不亏是盖曼
You could sense me.
被你发现我的气息了
Don't pull any punches, bring it on!
不必客气 来吧
I must get the flag!
必须抢下旗帜
Kasane, don't you remember the rules?
重 妳是不是忘记规则了
FAILURE
(失败)
VICTORY
(获胜)
Arashi!
岚
I'm exhausted.
没电了
This should be enough for training.
应该也训练够了吧
She is quite a handful.
真拿她没办法
Well done.
辛苦了
You did great too.
妳也辛苦了
You're not too shabby.
挺有一套的嘛
I felt the same when we last fought together.
上次跟你一起作战时 就这么觉得了
I appreciate the compliment.
谢谢夸奖…
But it takes more to earn my acknowledgment.
但 我还不会认同你
Whether you deserve my sister or not,
你究竟是否配得上姐姐
I'll keep observing.
我得再多多观察
What do you mean about observing?
观察什么
Excuse me, I have a message.
抱歉 我看一下讯息
Father?
爸爸
Congratulations on making it into the force.
恭喜你正式入伍
I'm still against the idea of you joining OSF.
虽然 我还是反对你进怪伐军
But at least don't get yourself hurt.
但至少别受伤了
Since you're a member of OSF now,
既然已是怪伐军的成员
that means you can hold your own.
就表示你也独当一面了
I want to use this opportunity
趁这个机会
to talk to you about our family and your late mother.
我想跟你聊聊 家里的事及你已逝世的母亲
We'll have dinner with Kaito another day.
下次找上界人 一起吃顿饭吧
I'll contact you again.
我再跟你联络
Kagero, your surprised me.
阳炎 真稀奇
What is it, Tsugumi?
我哪里稀奇了 鸫
I thought you hated training.
你不是讨厌训练吗
We don't have new members every day.
难得有菜鸟加入
Not to mention there are more girls joining our platoon this year.
而且今年加入的女孩子比较多
I have to make sure they see the awesome side of me.
所以我想展现帅气的一面啊
Deployment order.
出动命令
Other activities confirmed.
确认怪异出没
The location is the abandoned railway line of Suoh Nine.
地点在废弃地下轨道 苏芳九号线附近
Seto Platoon and Kyoka Platoon,
赛特小队 镜花小队
please deploy immediately.
请立刻出动
A lot of them fell from the Extinction Belt.
断绝之带下降了许多
The Others have got in through the air vents.
怪异似乎是从空调侵入
Communication devices might be affected here.
通讯机能可能会因此受到影响
Relying solely on telepathy without brain talk
光靠心电感应不使用脑部对话
will result in a one-way communication from me.
会变成我这边单方面跟大家对话
Let's pray the comms will work fine.
祈祷通讯机能维持良好状态
Seto Platoon, move out.
好 赛特小队前进
Kyoka Platoon, move out.
镜花小队前进
Hold on, Brother.
等一下 哥哥
What are you planning?
哥哥究竟在想什么
What is it that you seek?
到底看着什么
The past and future of this country.
这个国家的未来及过去
They are here!
来了
Scatter!
散开
Begin the attacks!
开始战斗
Captain, the communication disruption caused by the Extinction Belt is getting worse.
队长 断绝之带造成的通讯障碍 越来越…
At this rate...
再这样下去 不管要…
Understood. How is Kyoka Platoon doing?
渡 镜花队的状况如何
Wataru?
渡
Enemies from above, watch out!
上方 怪…快闪…
What was that? Haruka, repeat!
什么 遥 再说一次
They are attacking from above!
从上面的攻击要来了
Sister!
姊姊
Captain Kyoka.
镜花队长
Arashi, Shiden!
岚 紫电
Yuito, Nagi.
结人 那歧
It's Kasane and Naomi.
重 直见
Kasane, Naomi, are you all right?
重 直见 妳们没事吧
Tsugumi, where are Captain Seto and the rest?
鸫 赛特队长他们呢
We lost communication with them.
通讯机能连接不上
But I know they will be fine.
不过 他们一定没事
Where are Kyoka and the rest?
镜花他们呢
They can handle this level of enemies with ease.
这种程度的怪异奈何不了他们
They are here!
又来了
Naomi, watch out!
直见 危险
-Nagi! -Sister!
-那歧 -姊姊
Gemma, Tsugumi!
盖曼 鸫
Is everyone all right?
各位 没事吧
We are all right. What about the other two?
我们没事 另外两人呢
Where are Nagi and Naomi?
那歧和直见他们…
Sister!
姊姊…
I found them. They are in here.
找到了 在里面
Yuito, are you still there?
结人 你还活着吗
Nagi, where are you now?
那歧 你现在在哪
We're on the other side of these boulders.
穿过石块的隔壁
Naomi is with me.
直见跟我在一起
Nagi.
那歧
What is it, Nagi?
那歧 怎么了
The enemies are here!
怪异来了…
Sister!
姊姊
This is bad. They are surrounded by Others.
糟糕 怪异的数量太多
Connect the SAS cable.
链接SAS导线
Understood.
知道了
Let's give it a shot.
试试吧
Sister!
姊姊
Nagi, are you all right?
那歧 你没事吧
Sorry about that...
抱歉…
Sister!
姊姊
I'm all right, Kasane.
重 我没事
No!
不行
Kasane?
重
Kasane!
重…
Sister...
姊姊…
I'm glad you're safe.
太好了
Sister?
姊姊
What's wrong? Sister!
怎么了 姊姊
Let's move, Karen.
卡连 动作快
♪I don't need to let fate dictate me♪
无须被命运所指使
♪Because I believe that I can rewrite it♪
相信定会被改写
♪I'll always be a dreamer now and forever♪
让我们今后 继续做着梦
♪Another sunrise shines now and it blacks out♪
朝阳正光辉灿烂 随后落下
♪What's waiting for us at the world's end♪
在世界的尽头 究竟等着什么
♪Forever eternal, keep the fire going♪
未来 灯火永恒不灭
♪Who can shake us♪
谁在威胁我们
♪Who can define us♪
谁为我们决定
♪It's nothing less than our story♪
这是属于我们的故事
♪Forever eternal, keep the fire going in your heart♪
未来 你心中的灯火永恒不灭
CONSPIRACY
(阴谋)